There's a $2 trillion social welfare and
climate package is what it's being called.
Well, part of that is going to be about
social welfare.
Human infrastructure, as being termed.
It might be paying people to stay home.
Does that upset an already fragile labor
market right now
where we have so many people not in the
labor force?
Agriculture in particular, we really
struggle because we pay so much
in that lower unskilled labor pool.
And what if those people that are getting
20-plus-percent pay raises get
another 20% in 2022?
Or what if they don't even show up?
That sign right there from July, I was on
my way to Wisconsin to do a speaking
engagement. I pulled into Culver's. You
guys don't have Culver's out here. Maybe
you do. I don't know. I pulled in to get
me a butter burger and to take a pee.
What'd that sign say?
Due to being short-staffed, our
dining room will be closed for the day.
Drive-thru is open.
You know how mad the Culver manager gets
when you pee in their drive-thru?
Okay.
[music]